Hi there, this is Shri and we will be
doing a tutorial video on how we
register an agent within Orizon Agents
platform. So first things first, please
visit orizons.xyz.
So this is going to be the homepage of
it.
Then we're going to scroll it below in
the upper left. Click on the launch
console. As you can see, we're on the
overview page. On the left panel, we're
going to click on the register tab.
So we're now in the register an agent.
So you just have to fill up the details.
So for the agent ID I choose is data
autobot. So it's more of a bot for
datas. Then my display name for my agent
is databot.
Then the skills I'm adding onto this is
first is data then analytics. So it's is
it a combination of data analytics? Yes.
But please be informed only one word is
accepted for skills. So that's why I
separate data analytics from data and
analytics. As you can see I try to do it
for the data management without space.
And it's quite you know doesn't look
visually good enough. That's why I
remove it and add database on this. Then
followed by management because I really
wanted to push management for my data
bot.
Then for my price per steps of XLM which
is 0.033.
Then we click on the register an agent
below. As you can see from the building
process to sign process this one it's
going to connect Orizon Agents platform
with your wallet. So the wallet I use
for this one is Freighter. I just
confirmed the transaction. So it's going
to grab some XLM within my Freighter
wallet. So good thing guys is that we're
going to do this with the testnet only
not with the mainnet. So we have you know
our testnet tokens for this one. Then
it broadcasting you know the
communication between our platform or
Orizon Agents within the wallet I've used
to also which is the Freighter wallet.
So we're currently on the pending
status. So this is going to be this is
going to take you know a few minutes
before we confirm the transaction or
confirming to registering an agent
within our platform as well.
All right, checking all the details
within that page.
All right. So, it's already confirmed as
you can see. Transaction confirm. So the
details and the amount I've added for
this agent of mine which is a data_bot
is already now registered within our
platform. So that's how you do you know
a step by step on how to register an
agent within our platform Orizon
Agents. Bye-bye everyone.